<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scene on 2log</title>
    <link>https://yyyh123.github.io/tags/scene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scene on 2log</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yyyh123.github.io/tags/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://yyyh123.github.io/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yyyh123.github.io/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him. Presuming that he was some groom who had stolen in, the usher stopped him.
“Hold, my friend, you cannot pass!”
The man in the leather jerkin shouldered him aside.
“What does this knave want with me?” said he, in stentorian tones, which rendered the entire hall attentive to this strange colloquy. “Don’t you see that I am one of them?”
“Your name?” demanded the usher.
“Jacques Coppenole.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://yyyh123.github.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yyyh123.github.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning. It was neither an assault by the Picards nor the Burgundians, nor a hunt led along in procession, nor a revolt of scholars in the town of Laas, nor an entry of “our much dread lord, monsieur the king,” nor even a pretty hanging of male and female thieves by the courts of Paris. Neither was it the arrival, so frequent in the fifteenth century, of some plumed and bedizened embassy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
